[
	{
		"front": "개",
		"back": "Dog"
	},
	{
		"front": "고양이",
		"back": "Cat"
	},
	{
		"front": "물고기",
		"back": "Fish"
	},
	{
		"front": "새",
		"back": "Bird"
	},
	{
		"front": "말",
		"back": "Horse"
	},
	{
		"front": "쥐",
		"back": "Mouse"
	},
	{
		"front": "기린",
		"back": "Giraffe"
	},
	{
		"front": "소",
		"back": "Cow"
	},
	{
		"front": "원숭이",
		"back": "Monkey"
	},
	{
		"front": "돼지",
		"back": "Pig"
	},
	{
		"front": "토끼",
		"back": "Rabbit"
	},
	{
		"front": "뱀",
		"back": "Snake"
	},
	{
		"front": "코끼리",
		"back": "Elephant"
	},
	{
		"front": "닭",
		"back": "Chicken"
	},
	{
		"front": "강아지",
		"back": "Puppy"
	},
	{
		"front": "염소",
		"back": "Goat"
	},
	{
		"front": "양",
		"back": "Sheep"
	},
	{
		"front": "나비",
		"back": "Butterfly"
	},
	{
		"front": "게",
		"back": "Crab"
	},
	{
		"front": "늑대",
		"back": "Wolf"
	},
	{
		"front": "사슴",
		"back": "Deer"
	},
	{
		"front": "곰",
		"back": "Bear"
	},
	{
		"front": "여우",
		"back": "Fox"
	},
	{
		"front": "너구리",
		"back": "Raccoon"
	},
	{
		"front": "거북이",
		"back": "Turtle"
	},
	{
		"front": "개구리",
		"back": "Frog"
	},
	{
		"front": "상어",
		"back": "Shark"
	},
	{
		"front": "악어",
		"back": "Crocodile"
	},
	{
		"front": "고래",
		"back": "Whale"
	},
	{
		"front": "문어",
		"back": "Octopus"
	},
	{
		"front": "오징어",
		"back": "Squid"
	},
	{
		"front": "장어",
		"back": "Eel"
	},
	{
		"front": "앵무새",
		"back": "Parrot"
	},
	{
		"front": "까마귀",
		"back": "Crow"
	},
	{
		"front": "비둘기",
		"back": "Dove"
	},
	{
		"front": "매",
		"back": "Hawk"
	},
	{
		"front": "사자",
		"back": "Lion"
	},
	{
		"front": "호랑이",
		"back": "Tiger"
	},
	{
		"front": "도마뱀",
		"back": "Lizard"
	},
	{
		"front": "개미",
		"back": "Ant"
	},
	{
		"front": "달팽이",
		"back": "Snail"
	},
	{
		"front": "모기",
		"back": "Mosquito"
	}
]
